

# ANITA LAVRENTEVA

WEB DESIGNER | GRAPHIC DESIGNER | RETOUCHER

#### **PROFILE**

I'm a creative, sociable and versatile person. I have 5 years of experience in Design and Retouching including work experience in FinTech company. I love to work in a team and I'm always open to new opportunities. I follow new trends and styles. I try to learn something new and improve every day!

# **CONTACT**

Phone: +357 95 519101
Telegram: +7 923 316 5212
Address: Limassol, Cyprus

Email: Lavrenteva.Anita@yandex.ru

# **SKILLS**

Sketch
Photoshop
Illustrator
InDesign
XD

Figma

# **PORTFOLIO**

Website: anitalav.github.io/portfolio Behance: behance.net/anilav

Instagram: instagram.com/retouch.lav

# **SOCIAL NETWORKS**



@Ani.Lav



@AnitaLavrenteva

### **EDUCATION**

- Quality Assurance
   SkillUp | 2020
- MUA retouch. Advanced level
   RetouchingAcademy | 2019
- Beauty retouch. Advanced level
   Retouch\_Lera | 2019
- UX/UI designSkillbox | 2017
- Graphic design from scratch to PRO
   Skillbox | 2016
- Web-design from scratch to PRO
   Skillbox | 2016
- ACE Certificate "Adobe Certified Expert" Link Academy | 2015
- Diploma "Architecture and Design"
   Siberian Federal University | 2014 2018

#### **EXPERIENCE**

- UX/UI Designer "NBH Markets" | 05.2019 - 09.2020
- UX/UI Designer "UP Context" | 05.2018 - 03.2019
- Web Designer | Graphic Designer "Real Jump" | 03.2016 - 04.2018
- Private Practice / Freelance| 2015 2016

#### **INTEREST**









